http://www.guasfcu.com/privacy

Direct Deposit
Convenience Checks, Checkbooks, Money Orders and Cashier's Checks
Direct Deposit
Convenience Checks, Checkbooks,Money Orders and Cashier's Checks
Privacy Policy
Georgetown University Alumni and Student Federal Credit Union (“GUASFCU”) operates guasfcu.com. It is GUASFCU’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect. This policy is meant to be a supplement to any other agreement we have with you and does not supersede any of these agreements.
Website VisitorsLike most website operators, GUASFCU collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. GUASFCU’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how GUASFCU’s visitors use its website. From time to time, GUASFCU may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
GUASFCU also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP).
Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to GUASFCU’s websites choose to interact with GUASFCU in ways that require GUASFCU to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that GUASFCU gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a newsletter to provide a name, company and email address. In each case, GUASFCU collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with GUASFCU. GUASFCU does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated StatisticsGUASFCU may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, GUASFCU may monitor website usage information. GUASFCU may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, GUASFCU does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying InformationGUASFCU discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors, affiliated organizations, and third party services such as Google Analytics that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on GUASFCU’s behalf or to provide services available at GUASFCU’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors, affiliated organizations, and third party services may be located outside of your home country; by using GUASFCU’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. GUASFCU will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, GUASFCU discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when GUASFCU believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of GUASFCU, third parties or the public at large, or in order to provide marketing and/or services to customers or potential customers, or to collect and analyze information. If you have supplied your email address, GUASFCU may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with GUASFCU and our products. We expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. GUASFCU takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
CookiesA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. GUASFCU uses cookies to help GUASFCU identify and track visitors, their usage of GUASFCU website, and their website access preferences. GUASFCU visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using GUASFCU’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of GUASFCU’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Business TransfersIf GUASFCU, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that GUASFCU goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of GUASFCU may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
AdsWhile guasfcu.com does not display any third-party ads, cookies may be set by advertising partners in order to market GUASFCU’s products and services on other websites. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by GUASFCU and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertiser or network.
Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, GUASFCU may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in GUASFCU’s sole discretion. GUASFCU encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
202.687.8616
Lost Card?
© 2020 Georgetown University Alumni & Student Federal Credit Union. All Rights Reserved.
Federally insured by NCUA. Equal Housing Lender
